https://www.tmg.org.uk/privacy-policy-2018/

Skip to contentHome pageWho we areWho we areAn Invitation – VideoTrianon HeritagePhotograph ArchivePhotograph Archive (Login)Join UsJoin Trianon as a MemberJoin Trianon as a FriendJoin Trianon as a SponsorMembers InfoAnnual General MeetingRehearsal ScheduleTrianon NewslettersTrianon ToursSubscriptionsInformation for new choir membersInformation for new orchestra membersHealth and SafetyCommittees and MeetingsSafeguarding PolicyTrianon’s ValuesTrianon Music Group ConstitutionThanks and LinksProgramme ArchiveBuy ticketsContactDiamond JubileeOur 2019 commissionsPrivacy Policy 2018Trianon Music GroupData Privacy NoticeIntroductionIn order to operate, Trianon Music Group needs to gather, store and use certain forms ofinformation about individuals.These individuals include members, trustees, volunteers, occasional performers, audiences and  potential audiences, business contacts and other people the group has a relationship with or  regularly needs to contact.This notice explains how this data will be collected, stored and used in order to comply with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).Who and what does this notice apply to?This notice applies to all those handling personal data on behalf of Trianon Music Group, e.g. committee members, volunteers, contractors, 3rd party suppliers. It applies to all personal data that Trianon Music Group holds relating to individuals, including:NamesEmail addressesPostal addressesPhone numbersAny other personal information held, including financial informationRoles and responsibilitiesEveryone who has access to personal data as part of Trianon Music Group has a responsibility to ensure that they adhere to this policy.Data controllerThe Data Controller for Trianon Music Group is its Management Committee. They are responsible for deciding why data is collected and how it will be used. Any questions relating to the collection or use of data should be directed to the Data Controller c/o The Administrator.How we fairly and lawfully process your personal dataTrianon Music Group will only collect data where lawful and where it is necessary for thelegitimate purposes of the group.A member’s name and contact details will be collected when they first join the group, and will be used to contact them regarding membership administration, news, events and activities. Other data may subsequently be collected in relation to their membership, including their payment history for subs. Data may be shared with HMRC for gift aid purposes, if you have completed a gift aid form.The name, contact details and date of birth of Trustees of Trianon Music Group will be collected when they first take up a position, and will be shared, as required by legal obligation, with the Charity Commission. These details will also be used to contact them regarding group administration related to their role. Personal details of cheque signatories may also be shared with the relevant banks and financial institutions.The name and contact details of other volunteers will be collected when they first take up a position, and will be used to contact them regarding group administration related to their role.Further information, including personal financial information, may also be collected in specific circumstances where lawful and necessary, in order to process payment to a person.An individual’s name and contact details will be collected when they purchase tickets for an event. These details may be used to contact them about their ticket purchase and allow them entry to the event.An individual’s name, contact details and other details may be collected at any time (eg. additional concert performers, who are not members), with their consent, in order for Trianon Music Group to communicate with them about concerts, future concerts and other group activities.How we use your personal informationWhen collecting data, Trianon Music Group will always explain to the subject why the data is required and what it will be used for. We will never use data for any purpose other than that stated or that can be considered reasonably to be related to it. For example, we may pass your name and address to the printer of the newsletter in order to distribute newsletters.Disclosure of your personal informationTrianon Music Group will never pass on personal data to un-connected 3rd parties without your explicit consent.Further ProcessingIf we wish to use your data for a new purpose, then we will provide you with a new noticeexplaining this new use prior to commencing the processing, and setting out the relevant purposes and processing conditions. We will seek your prior consent to the new processing.Relevance, accuracy and retentionTrianon Music Group will not collect or store more data that the minimum information required for its intended purpose, and will ask members, trustees and committee members, and volunteers, to check and update their data on an annual basis. Any individual will be able to update their data at any point by contacting the Data Controller. Trianon Music Group will keep data on individuals for no longer than 3 years after our involvement with the individual has stopped, unless there is a legal requirement to keep records. Paper copies will be destroyed and electronic copies deleted. Financial records and any personal data attached to them will be retained for six years plus the current financial year.How we store your personal dataTrianon Music Group will ensure that data held by us is kept secure.Electronically-held data will be held within a password-protected and secure environment Passwords for electronic data files will be re-set each time an individual with data access leaves their role/positionPhysically-held data (e.g. membership forms, gift aid forms or email sign-up sheets) and backup storage will be stored in a secure mannerAccess to data will only be given to relevant trustees/committee members/volunteers where it is clearly necessary for the running of the group. The Data Controller will decide in what situations this is applicable and will keep a master list of who has access to data.Your rightsThe following requests can be made in writing to the Data Controller:Individuals whose personal data is held by Trianon Music Group can request to see any data stored about them. Any such request will be complied with within 28 days of the request being received.Individuals whose personal data is held by Trianon Music Group can request that any inaccurate data held on them is updated. Any such request will be complied with within 28 days of the request being received.Individuals whose personal data is held by Trianon Music Group can request that any data held on them is deleted. Any such request will be complied with within 28 days of the request being received.Individuals whose personal data is held by Trianon Music Group have the right to lodge a complaint with the Information Commissioner’s Office.Website CookiesCookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behaviour information. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity. All visitor tracking is anonymous.For further information visit www.aboutcookies.org or www.allaboutcookies.org. You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser. However in a few cases some of our website features may not function as a result.Other websitesOur website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies.Contact detailsTo exercise all relevant rights, queries or complaints, please, in the first instance, contact the Trianon Music Group administrator: dominique.nightingale@btinternet.comYou can contact the Information Commissioner’s Office on 0303 123 1113 or via emailhttps://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/email/ or at the Information Commissioner’s Office, Wycliffe House, Water Lane, Wilmslow, Cheshire. SK9 5AF.Updated August 2018Latest News Graham RansonGraham Ranson, well-known cellist and member of a number of Festive gatheringAs Christmas Day and New Year’s Day both fall on FRIDAY NIGHTS with TMGFriday 4 December Trianon Quiz Night (2) Mike Madden hosts New TMG Concerts announcedEach concert has a different programme featuring a selection of musicians from Trianon Music Group. Colin WrightColin Wright – Tenor has sadly passed away.Follow Us on TwitterTweets by @MusicTrianon Who are we?https://youtu.be/3Yh_cEXcIQQJoin UsJoin Trianon Here New members, Friends of Trianon and Sponsors welcomeTicket Booking LineCall the Trianon Ticket Line:01394 283170 or07876 7870292020 Season ProgrammeConcert Season 2020 Events and concerts at Ipswich Corn Exchange and other venues for 2020PhotosView Our Flickr AlbumPhotos of concerts and Trianon social eventsTrianon on Tour – Warwickshire 2019Trianon Music Group, Ipswich, Suffolk, UK Reg.charity no.276715Founded in Ipswich during 1959 A member of Ipswich Arts Association www.ipswich-arts.org.ukAffiliated to: Anglia Singers, Essex; Crescendo, France; L’Esperance, The NetherlandsPresident: John Rutter CBE Artistic Director and Conductor: Emeritus Professor Christopher Green OBE Chairman: Simon Fisher Vice Chair: Nigel KingContactData Privacy NoticeSafeguarding Policy
CookiesThis site uses cookies: Find out more.Okay, thank you
